Sophie Treadwell papers, 1860s-1970 (bulk 1910-1960)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series VIII: Photographic materials, ca. 1860s-1960s
  - Helene Modjeska and Bozeta Chalapowski. 1897, 1908 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Robert A. Parker (?); Gaby Pelletier; Luther Sutherland. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Unidentified males. (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Profile, seated with chair, Portrait of Sophie Treadwell by Sherril Schell. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Profile, face close-up, Portrait of Sophie Treadwell by Sherril Schell. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Profile, black blouse, outdoors, Portrait of Sophie Treadwell by Sherril Schell. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Full face, turned over right shoulder, scarf, Portrait of Sophie Treadwell by Sherril Schell. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Profile, lace shawl, Portrait of Sophie Treadwell by Sherril Schell. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Profile, front partial figure, scarf, Portrait of Sophie Treadwell by Sherril Schell. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Profile, flowered blouse, Portrait of Sophie Treadwell by Sherril Schell. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Double profile, Portrait of Sophie Treadwell by Sherril Schell. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Profile, scarf on left shoulder, Portrait of Sophie Treadwell by Sherril Schell. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Full face, partial figure, scarf, Portrait of Sophie Treadwell by Sherril Schell. (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Full face, geometric blouse, Portrait of Sophie Treadwell by Sherril Schell. (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Full figure, outdoors, Portrait of Sophie Treadwell by Sherril Schell. (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Series IX: Supplemental materials, ca. 1915-1950s
  - Posters
    - Poster: "An Unwritten Chapter," Pantages Theater, San Francisco, [oversize: located in flat files]. 1915 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Posters (3): " Machinal," Russian productions, [oversize: located in flat files]. 1933 (Box 23, Folder 14-16)
  - Art Objects
    - Drawing: of Treadwell (?) signed Maria Langtree. (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Gouache: woman, city building, signed "R-P" (Robert P. Allerton ?). (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Gouache: Cacti (attributed to A.L. Searles). (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Watercolor: "Cafe Brocart," Unidentified Artist. (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Drawing: Arthur Hopkins, by Marcus? 1933 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Painting: tin retablo: Virgin of Guadalupe. (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Gouache, pen and ink: "And a Little Child Shall Lead Them," San Francisco Bulletin staff to Sophie Treadwell, [located in flat files]. 1915 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Paintings: "The Light Thou Givest Me"; "Dawn,", attributed to Maynard Dixon. November 11 and 13, 1916 (Box 23, Folder 24-25)
    - Paintings: unattributed "B.E." series found in Rimrock and Sage covers. (Box 23, Folder 26-32)
  - Motion Picture Film
    Two seven-inch reels, silent, black and white, ca. early 1930s. Selective synopsis.
    - Street scenes and traveling footage of car going down highway in New York City and Washington D.C.; different journeys by car, one through oil country in South-west?; ends with snow skiers going up and down slopes. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Street scenes and traveling footage of car going down highway in New York City and Washington D.C.; different journeys by car, one through oil country in South-west?; ends with snow skiers going up and down slopes, DVD Access Copy. (Box 24, Folder 1A)
    - Sophie Treadwell walking by; poolside with Treadwell in chair; William McGeehan with car; touring by car in Germany, youth group walks by with flag, country villages, ferry boat arrival, scenes on board, docking; Treadwell with dogs. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Sophie Treadwell walking by; poolside with Treadwell in chair; William McGeehan with car; touring by car in Germany, youth group walks by with flag, country villages, ferry boat arrival, scenes on board, docking; Treadwell with dogs, DVD Access Copy. (Box 24, Folder 2B)
  - Artifacts
    - Luggage. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Still camera: Zeiss Ikon and case. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Motion camera: Siemens and case. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Pistol holster, stamped U.S. Army. (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Series X: William O'Connell McGeehan Papers, 1900-1933
  - Correspondence and Personal Materials
    - Correspondence and condolences. 1925-1933 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Passport and service medals. 1899-1933 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Works
    See also additional McGeehan materials: Correspondence, Box 5; Scrapbook, Box 15; Photographs, Box 21.
    - The Appointment. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Consuelo's Army. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - The Enchanted Carrot. ca. 1925 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Hunger. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - The Man Who Wanted the South; The Pain of the World. 1900 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - A Matter of Theology. ca. 1925 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - The Squeeze Play. (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - A Two Dollar Bill. (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - The Winner's End. (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Titles unkown. (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Articles: from his sports columns, "Down the Line." (Box 26, Folder 13)